export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Where did we go on our first date?",
    answer: 'Sto\'s'
  },
  {
    question: "Where did you live when we first met?",
    answer: 'Fishtown'
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the musical we were coming back from when the old guy yelled at you for gas?",
    answer: 'The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee'
  },
  {
    question: "What show did we watch when we built the blanket fort?",
    answer: "Stranger Things"
  },
  {
    question: "What show were we gathering to meet our first few times meeting?",
    answer: "Game of Thrones"
  },
  {
    question: "What was the first mountain you skied in Colorado?",
    answer: 'Copper'
  },
  {
    question: "How many New Years have we celebrated together? (in number form)",
    answer: '3'
  },
  {
    question: "What word did you discover you hate?",
    answer: 'Slalom'
  },
  {
    question: "What's my second favorite primary color?",
    answer: 'Green'
  },
  {
    question: "What's my favorite holiday?",
    answer: "Christmas"
  },
  
  {
    question: "How much I love you",
    answer: "more"
  },
]